Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The UAW..a union that gives service, 1985; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The UAW..a union that gives service, 1985; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: What do students learn about labor, Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: UAW Administrative Letter, 1978; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30: letter no. 2
  - Item 9: What's in a typical UAW contract, Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: You and the UAW: for local union leadership and membership, 1990; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Building effective local union Educationa Programs, 1990; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Building effective local union Educationa Programs, 1990; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Case of the workplace killers: a manual for cancer detectives on the job, 1981; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
    Author: Michael Silverstein; Education Deparment
  - Item 14: Our Past: The challenges ahead, new directions new dimensions, 1985; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: The trade crisis and the U.S. economy, 1985; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: The trade crisis and the U.S. economy, 1985; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Michigan State Public Employes: grievance handbook, 1986; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Michigan State Public Employes: grievance handbook, 1986; Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: article - UAW is a clean union, Publication (Box 504, Folder 2)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 504, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Youand your membership in the UAW, 1974; Publication (Box 504, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: New UAW member orientation - initiation, Publication (Box 504, Folder 3)
    Notes: Material from 'new member kit'. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local union bargaining and grievance representatives answer book, 1992; Publication (Box 504, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Local union bargaining and grievance representatives answer book, 1992; Publication (Box 504, Folder 3)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 504, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Staff of the New-York Historical Society is on strike, Publication (Box 504, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The attached Employee Investment Plan Summary Plan Description is intended to provide you with a plain language explanation of the EIP, 1983; Publication (Box 504, Folder 4)
    Notes: Correspondence.
  - Item 3: The attached Employee Investment Plan Summary Plan Description is intended to provide you with a plain language explanation of the EIP, 1983; Publication (Box 504, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: UAW-AMC Report - April 1982, Publication (Box 504, Folder 4)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: To All laid off workers!, Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: To All laid off workers!, Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
    Notes: Advertisement. Copy 2
  - Item 3: Using credit wisely!, Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1968; Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Easing your credit crunch!, Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Consumers' manual for setting up effective local union/CAP Council.., Publication (Box 504, Folder 5)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Corporate Farm, 1987; Publication (Box 505, Folder 1)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Is time study scientific?, 1972; Publication (Box 505, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Grievance handlers' pocket guide, 1991; Publication (Box 505, Folder 2)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UAW outlaws discrimination, 1946; Publication (Box 505, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The ordeal of Bobby Cain, 1956; Publication (Box 505, Folder 3)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Work Live Review, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1982)
  - Item 2: The Work Live Review, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1982). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UAW-Ford Report, 1987; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1987.
  - Item 4: UAW-Ford Report, 1997; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1997.
  - Item 5: 1987 Negotiations fact book for news media, Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: UAW-Ford Mutual Growth Forum, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: Workbook.
  - Item 7: UAW-Ford Mutual Growth Forum, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 4)
    Notes: Workbook. Copy 2.
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: UAW and GM Launch Health and Safety Study, 1984; Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Minority Report: An analysis of the short-comings of the 1984 General Motors Contract, Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: UAW-GM Human Resource Center, 1986; Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: AIDS information network: joint administrative summary, 1988; Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Dealing with AIDS, 1988; Publication (Box 505, Folder 5)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Thirty-five items to consider for a safety inspection, Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Your right to know, hazard communication guidelines: a guide to chemical hazards and health & safety in the workplace., 1986-1988 (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Your right to know, hazard communication guidelines: a guide to chemical hazards and health & safety in the workplace., 1986-1988 (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: What every UAW representative should know about health & safety, 1979; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
    Author: Social Security Department
  - Item 5: What every UAW representative should know about health & safety, 1979; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Guide to visual display units, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
    Author: Barrie E. Brooks
  - Item 7: Guide to visual display units, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Strains & sprains: a worker's guide to job design, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
    Author: Dan MacLeod
  - Item 9: Strains & sprains: a worker's guide to job design, 1982; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: The Hazards of lead and how to control them, 1980; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
    Author: Health and Safety Department
  - Item 11: The Hazards of lead and how to control them, 1980; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: The Lead battery industry: a worker's guide to controlling the lead hazard, 1980; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The Lead battery industry: a worker's guide to controlling the lead hazard, 1980; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Lead hazards in vehicle assembly and repair operations body solder, 1977; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Lead hazards in vehicle assembly and repair operations body solder, 1977; Publication (Box 505, Folder 6)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Leonard Woodcock, unionist & citizen, 1991; Publication (Box 505, Folder 7)
    Author: John Barnard
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Strategies against shutdowns: a UAW plant closing manual (for confidential use of UAW International Representatives), 1981; Publication (Box 505, Folder 8)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Affirmative Action Program for Apprenticeship Training, 1980; Publication (Box 505, Folder 9)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Congressional Legislative Alert, 1992; Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
    Author: Legislative Department
    Notes: September 16, 1992.
  - Item 2: Statement of Alan Reutherbefore the Subcommittee on Trade Committee on Ways and Means United States House of Representatives on Impact of the North American Free Trade Agreement (Sept. 22, 1992), Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Washington Report, 1991; Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.32 (1991:Nov. 15)
  - Item 4: Congressional Legislative Alert, 1992; Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
    Notes: October 9, 1992.
  - Item 5: A history in words and pictures of Amalgamate Local 686, UAW, 40th Anniv., 1979; Publication (Box 505, Folder 10)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Meeting the challenges of the future with peopleour greatest resource, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Meeting the challenges of the future with peopleour greatest resource, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Notes: Flyer. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Don't let South Africa hang this labor leaderMoses Mayekiso, 1987; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Don't let South Africa hang this labor leaderMoses Mayekiso, 1987; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: SOLID Fax, 1996; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 30, 1996.
  - Item 6: SOLID Fax, 1996; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 14, 1996.
  - Item 7: SOLID Fax, 1996; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 10, 1996.
  - Item 8: SOLID Fax, 1996; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 24, 1996.
  - Item 9: Joint Process in selected General Motors Plants, 1988; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: UAW-GM Human Resource Center, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Action strategy summary - April 1991, Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Guidelines to employe involvement, 1987; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Author: Local 652
  - Item 13: UAW-Ford Employe involvement: a special survey report, 1983; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
    Author: Ford Motor Division
  - Item 14: Quality of work life: "What's in a name?", 1978; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Quality of work life: Guidelines, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Jointness in GM/UAW relationships at plant level, 1988; Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: UAW a union for all workers: it doesn't cost to belong to the UAW, it pays, Publication (Box 506, Folder 1)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Next 50 years -- workshop folder, Publication (Box 506, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Ford Romeo Engine Plant: team building, launch training and employee relations, 1990; Publication (Box 506, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Putting people back together, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 2)
    Author: Frederick Herzberg
  - Item 4: Right brain, left brain; fact and fiction (reprinted from Psychology Today, May 1985), Publication (Box 506, Folder 2)
    Author: Jerre Levy
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Case of the workplace killers: a manual for cancer detectives on the job, 1981; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated local unions in the UAW, 1990; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: News from the UAW. Permanent job security, full Union/Management Partnership in New UAW-Saturn Small car agreement, 1985; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
    Notes: Press release. Photocopy.
  - Item 4: A look at the past: High School Labor Studies - Union History, 1992; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Child Care: a handbook for working parents, Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
    Notes: Collection of pamphlets telling about child care.
  - Item 6: A strong Union in a changing world: UAW: the report of the Commission on the Future of the UAW, 1989; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: A strong Union in a changing world: UAW: the report of the Commission on the Future of the UAW, 1989; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Our working future: a guide to new technology, 1985; Publication (Box 506, Folder 3)
    Author: Skilled Trades Department
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Planning for successful living: a UAW pre-retirement program, 1980; Publication (Box 506, Folder 4)
    Author: Retired and Older Workers Department
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Summary of the UAW-Jeep: 1990-1997 tentative settlement (Box 506, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Special UAW Report - August, November 1992, Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: UAW-Deere & Co.: highlights of proposed new agreement 1991-1994 (Box 506, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The naked truth about unions, 1986; Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
    Notes: This brochure is based on vol. 24, no. 1 of UAW AMMO
  - Item 5: Newsbrief: a digest of news about the UAW, its programs and industries, and vital public issues, 1992; Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
    Author: Public Relations and Publications Department
  - Item 6: The Outrageous adventures of George and Dan, 1992; Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
    Notes: Comic book
  - Item 7: The Outrageous adventures of George and Dan, 1992; Publication (Box 506, Folder 5)
    Notes: Comic book. Copy 2.
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Joint venture/UAW letter of intent, 1983; Publication (Box 506, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Joint venture/UAW letter of intent, 1983; Publication (Box 506, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Special Report to the Membership. UAW-NUMMI, 1985; Publication (Box 506, Folder 6)
    Notes: June 1985.
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 506, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: UAW, IAM and USWA announce unification as new union by year 2000, 1995; Publication (Box 506, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: UAW, IAM and USWA announce unification as new union by year 2000, 1995; Publication (Box 506, Folder 7)
    Notes: Press release. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Unity Declaration of the IAM, UAW, and USWA, 1995; Publication (Box 506, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 27, 1995. Inter-Office Memo
  - Item 4: Unity Declaration of the IAM, UAW, and USWA, 1995; Publication (Box 506, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 27, 1995. Inter-Office Memo. Copy 2.